Guide to the David L. Call papers, 1977-1995.
Call, David L. papers, 1977-1995
- Long Island Horticultural Research Laboratory--Advisory Council, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 49)
- M (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 50)
- M (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 51)
- Mann Library, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Mann Library, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Media Services, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Media Services, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Microbiology, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Migrants, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Migrants, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Minorities, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Minority Graduate Student & Faculty Recruitment, Committee to Monitor, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Minority Graduate Student & Faculty Recruitment, Committee to Monitor, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Minority Resources Development Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- N (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Neurobiology & Behavior, Section of, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Northeast Dairy Compact, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Northeast Regional Center for Rural Development, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Nutritional Sciences, Division of, 1987-1989 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Nutritional Sciences, Division of, 1987-1989 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- NY Farm Bureau, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- NY Farm Bureau, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- NY Labor Study, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- NY Seed Improvement Cooperative, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva--Audit Report, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva--Director's Office (Robert Plane), 1989 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva--Director's Office (Robert Plane), 1989 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva--Entomolgy Dept., 1989 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva--Food Science & Technology Dept., 1989 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva--Horticultural Sciences Dept., 1989 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva--Plant Pathology Dept., 1989 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- NYS Dept. of Agriculture & Markets, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- NYS Dept. of Agriculture & Markets, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- NYS Assembly, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- NYS Dept. of Environmental Conservation, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- NYS Dept. of Environmental Conservation, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- NYS Fair, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- NYS Green Council, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- NYS Green Council, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 41)
- NYS Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 42)
- NYS Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 43)
- NYS Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 44)
- O (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 45)
- Olin Foundation, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 46)
- Organic Foods, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 47)
- P (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- PACNYS (Professional Agricultural Consultants of NYS, Inc.), 1989 (Box 40, Folder 49)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Management Program, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 50)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Management Program, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 51)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Management Program, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 52)
- Physiology, Section of, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 53)
- Plant Biology, Section of, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 54)
- Plant Breeding & Biometry, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 55)
- Plant Breeding & Biometry, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 56)
- Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Pomology (Ithaca & Geneva), 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Population & Development Program (International Population Program), 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Poultry & Avian Sciences, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Presidential Scholars, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Pro-Fac Cooperative, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- (Vice) Provost--Barry Adams, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Provost--Robert Barker, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Provost--Robert Barker, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Provost--Robert Barker, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Provost--Robert Barker, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Provost--Robert Barker, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Provost--Robert Barker, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Provost--Malden Nesheim, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Provost--Malden Nesheim, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Provost--Malden Nesheim, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Provost--Malden Nesheim, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Provost--Malden Nesheim, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Provost--Malden Nesheim, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Provost--Malden Nesheim--Thornfield Retreat, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Provost--Malden Nesheim--Thornfield Retreat, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Public Affairs, Office of, 1988-1990 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Public Affairs, Office of (Lael C. Carter, Associate Director, Development), 1989 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Public Affairs, Office of (Richard Ramin, Vice President), 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- R (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Research, Office for, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Research, Office for, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Research, Office for, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Research & Advanced Studies (Joseph Ballantyne, Vice President), 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Research & Advanced Studies (David Brown, Associate Director for Research), 1987-1989 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Research & Advanced Studies (B.F.. Chabot, Acting Director), 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- Research & Advanced Studies (B.F.. Chabot, Acting Director), 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- Research & Advanced Studies (Norm Scott, Vice President), 1987-1989 (Box 41, Folder 35)
- Research & Advanced Studies (Norm Scott, Vice President), 1987-1989 (Box 41, Folder 36)
- Retirement, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 37)
- Rhodes, Frank, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 37)
- Rhodes, Frank, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 38)
- Rhodes, Frank, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 39)
- Rhodes, Frank, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 40)
- Roby Athletic Comittee, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 41)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 42)
- Rural Schools Program, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 43)
- Rural Schools Program, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 44)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 45)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 46)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 47)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of--Chairmanship, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 48)
- S (General Correspondence), 1989 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Salaries, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- SBEEP (Small Business Energy Effiiciency Program), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Science, Technology, & Society, Program on--Annual Report to the Provost), 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Sea Grant Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Sea Grant Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Senators, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Sheep Task Force, 1986-1989 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Soil, Crop, & Atmospheric Sciences, Dept. of, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Soviet Union--Exchange Program, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Sponsored Programs, Office of (T. Rogers), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Statutory College Affairs (Nathan Fawcett, Director), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Statutory College Affairs (Nathan Fawcett, Director), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Statutory College Affairs (Nathan Fawcett, Director), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Students, Dean of, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Sustainable Agriculture, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Sustainable Agriculture, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- T (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Tetra-Pak Agreement, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Tunison Laboratory, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- U (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Undergraduate Education, Cornell Commission on, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Undergraduate Education, Cornell Commission on, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Undergraduate Education, Subcommittee on Curricular Innovation Commission, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- University Counsel, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- University Relations (John Burness, Vice President), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- University Relations (John Burness, Vice President), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- University Relations (John Burness, Vice President), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- University Relations (John Burness, Vice President), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 29)
- University Relations (John Burness, Vice President), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 30)
- University Relations (John Burness, Vice President), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 31)
- USDA, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 32)
- USDA--Interagency Agreement on Forestry, 1978-1989 (Box 42, Folder 33)
- V (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 34)
- Vegetable Crops, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 35)
- Vegetable Crops & Pomology & Fruit and Vegetable Science--Dept. Consolidation, 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 36)
- Vice President, Senior (James E. Morley, Jr.), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 37)
- Vice President & Treasurer, Office of (Fred Rogers, Vice President for Finance and Treasurer), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 38)
- W (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 39)
- Waste Management Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 40)
- Waste Management Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 41)
- Waste Management Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 42)
- Waste Management Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 43)
- Waste Management Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 44)
- Watershed Agricultural Program--New York City, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 45)
- Willsboro Health Center, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 46)
- Wing, Kenneth E. (Associate Dean), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 47)
- Wing, Kenneth E. (Associate Dean), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 48)
- Wing, Kenneth E. (Associate Dean), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 49)
- Wing, Kenneth E. (Associate Dean), 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 50)
- Winrock International Institute, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Wolf Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- World Center, 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Z (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Zuidema, Larry (Acting Director, International Agrigulture Program), 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- A (General Correspondence), 1990 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Academic Programs, Office of, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Academic Programs, Office of (George Conneman, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Academic Programs, Office of (Elizabeth Oltenacu, Associate Director), 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Academic Programs & Campus Affairs, Office of, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- ACUSNY (Association of Colleges & Universities of the State of New York), 1991 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Administrative Services, 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Administrative Services, 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Administrative Services, 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Administrative Services, 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Admissions, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Admissions & Financial Aid (Susan Murphy, Dean), 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Affirmative Action, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Agricultural & Biological Engineering, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Agricultural & Biological Engineering, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Agricultural & Biological Engineering, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1990-199 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Agricultural Library, Associates of the National, 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Agricultural Protection Act (Right to Farm Bill), 1991 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Agricultural Reserch Initiative, National, 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Agriculture, Advisory Council on, 1987-1991 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Agriculture in the Classroom, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Agrotechnics, Inc., 1990 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- AgSat (Agricultural Satellite Corporation), 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- AgSat (Agricultural Satellite Corporation), 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 30)
- AgSat (Agricultural Satellite Corporation), 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- AgSat (Agricultural Satellite Corporation), 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 32)
- Agway, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 33)
- Alexander von Humboldt Foundation Award, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 34)
- Alpha Gamma Rho, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 35)
- Alumni & Development (John Sterling, Director of Alumni Affairs), 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 36)
- Alumni & Development (John Sterling, Director of Alumni Affairs), 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 37)
- Alumni Association--Communications Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 38)
- American Indian Agriculture Project, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 39)
- American Indian Program, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 40)
- American Indian Program, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 41)
- American Indian Program, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 42)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 43)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 44)
- Animal Science/USSR Training, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 45)
- Arnot Forest, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 46)
- Asia (Southeast) Program, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 47)
- Asia (Southeast) Program, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 48)
- Athletic Department, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 49)
- Audit Report (CALS), 1991 (Box 43, Folder 50)
- Awards, 1981-1991 (Box 43, Folder 51)
- B (General Correspondence) (Edward Bernays), 1985-1991 (Box 43, Folder 52)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 53)
- Biochemistry, Molecular & Cell Biology, Section of, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Biological Sciences, Division of, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- bST (artificial bovine hormone), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- C (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- CARAFE (Coalition for Advancement of Research on Agriculture, Food & Environment), 1990-1992 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- CaRDI (Community and Rural Development Institute), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- CaRDI (Community and Rural Development Institute), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- CaRDI (Community and Rural Development Institute), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Career Development, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Carter, Harvey, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Chemicals/Pesticides Program, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- CIIFAD--Correspondence (Cornell International Institute for Food, Agriculture, & Development), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- CIIFAD--Correspondence (, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- CIIFAD--Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- CIIFAD--Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- CIIFAD--Correspondence (, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- CIIFAD--Environmental & Natural Resources, Study Committee on, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- CIIFAD--Executive Committee, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- CIIFAD--External Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- CIIFAD--News Releases, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- CIIFAD--Research Policy Committee, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- CIIFAD--Sustainable Agriculture Committee, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Cohn Farm, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 31)
- Cohn Farm, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 32)
- Communication Arts, Dept. of, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 33)
- Communication Arts, Dept. of--PhD Program, 1990-1992 (Box 44, Folder 34)
- Communication Arts, Dept. of--PhD Program, 1990-1992 (Box 44, Folder 35)
- Communication Arts, Dept. of--PhD Program, 1990-1992 (Box 44, Folder 36)
- Congress Members, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 37)
- Controller, Office of the, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 38)
- Cooperative Extension, 1989-1991 (Box 44, Folder 39)
- Cooperative Extension, 1989-1991 (Box 44, Folder 40)
- Cooperative Extension (Lucinda Noble, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 41)
- Cooperative Extension (Lucinda Noble, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 42)
- Cooperative Extension (R. David Smith, Associate Director), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 43)
- Cornell Abroad, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 44)
- Cornell Plantations, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 45)
- Cornell Plantations--Personnel, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 46)
- Corporate Development & Foundation Relations, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 47)
- County Agents, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 48)
- County Law 224, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 49)
- D (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 50)
- D (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 51)
- Dairy Markets & Policy (Andrew Novakovic, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Dairy Records, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Dean, Assistant (William Boldt), 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Development Office (Dave Dunlop, Director of Capital Projects), 1991 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- E (General Correspondence) (Alfalfa Snout Beetle Project), 1991 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Earth Year, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Ecology & Systematics, Section of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Ecology & Systematics, Section of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Ecology & Systematics, Section of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Education, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Education, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Education, US Dept. of, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- (Cornell) Education Network (CEN), 1991 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- (Teacher) Education in Science & Math Program (TESM), 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- (Teacher) Education in Science & Math Program (TESM), 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Environment, Center for the, 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Environment, Center for the, 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Environmental Sciences, Study Committee on, 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Environmental Sciences, Study Committee on, 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Equal Opportunity, Office of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Executive Policy Review Group, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- F (General Correspondence), 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Facilities, Statutory Office for Capital, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Faculty, Economic Status of Statutory--Committee on, 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Farm Bill, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Farm Bill, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Farm Bill, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 30)
- Farm Bill, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 31)
- Farm Safety Program, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 32)
- Farm Services, 1985-1990 (Box 45, Folder 33)
- Farming Alternatives Program, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 34)
- Finance & Business Office, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 35)
- Finance & Business Office, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 36)
- Finance & Personnel (Nancy Hicks, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 37)
- Financial Aid, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 38)
- Financial Report, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 39)
- Fish & Wildlife Cooperative Units, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 40)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 41)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 42)
- (Roland) Foley Professorship Endowment, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 43)
- Food Safety, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 44)
- Food Science, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 45)
- Food Science Institute, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 46)
- Food Science Institute--Advisory Council, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 47)
- 4-H, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 48)
- Fredonia Property (photos enclosed), 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 49)
- Fredonia Property (photos enclosed), 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 50)
- Frosty Hill Fellowship (Dr. Forrest "Frosty" Hill), 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 51)
- Fruit & Vegetable Industry Committee, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 52)
- Fruit & Vegetable Science, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 53)
- G (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 54)
- Gamma Sigma Delta, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 55)
- Game Farm, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 56)
- Golf Course Management Program (Robert Trent Jones), 1987-1991 (Box 45, Folder 57)
- Golf Course Management Program (Robert Trent Jones), 1987-1991 (Box 45, Folder 58)
- Golf Course Management Program (Robert Trent Jones), 1987-1991 (Box 45, Folder 59)
- Government Affairs, Office of (Robert Barlow), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Government Affairs, Office of (Robert Barlow), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Government Affairs, Office of (Cecelia Roland), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Governor, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Governor, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Graduate School, 1988-1991 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Graduate School, 1988-1991 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Graduate School, 1988-1991 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Graduate School--Study Committee on, 1982-1991 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Graduate School--Study Committee on, 1982-1991 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Graduate School--Study Committee on, 1982-1991 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Graduate Students, CALS, 1990-1992 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- H (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- H (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Hansen Property, 1990-1992 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Hatfield Fellows, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Henry (Rene A.) vs Cornell University, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Honduras, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Hubert H. Humphrey Fellowships, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Hudson Valley Laboratory, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Human Relations (Joycelyn Hart, Associate Vice President), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Human Resource Development Council, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Human Resource Development Council, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- ICET (Institute for Comparative and Environmental Toxicology), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 24)
- ICET (Institute for Comparative and Environmental Toxicology), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 29)
- International Agriculture, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 30)
- International Agriculture, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 31)
- International Memoranda of Agreement, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- International Rice Research Institute, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 33)
- International Studies, Mario Einaudi Center for, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 34)
- J (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- K (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 36)
- Kellogg Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 37)
- Knight Foundation, 1990-1992 (Box 46, Folder 38)
- Korea--Seoul National University, 1990-1993 (Box 46, Folder 39)
- Krakow, Poland, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 40)
- L (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 41)
- Landscape Architecture Program, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 42)
- Landscape Architecture Reaccreditation, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 43)
- Libraries, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 44)